{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 3)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{2x + 3} * {2x + 3}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer."},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer."},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{3x + 1}*{3x + 4}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer."},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 18x + 5)/(6x^2 + 17x + 12)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{3x + 4}*{3x + 5}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{3x + 4} * {3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 12x + 5)/(9x^2 + 21x + 10)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}*{2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{3x + 1}*{2x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 19x + 10)/(4x^2 + 8x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{2x + 1} * {3x + 2}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 1}/{2x + 5}*{3x + 5}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{3x + 1} * {3x + 1}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{2x + 1}*{2x + 5}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{3x + 5} * {3x + 5}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1} * {3x + 1}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{3x + 4}*{3x + 2}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 1}/{3x + 2}*{3x + 5}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5} * {2x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 15x + 4)/(9x^2 + 21x + 10)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{2x + 3} * {2x + 3}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5} * {2x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{3x + 5} * {3x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 4)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{2x + 5}*{3x + 4}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{3x + 4}*{2x + 1}/{2x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{2x + 3}*{2x + 1}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{3x + 1}*{3x + 4}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 25x + 25)/(6x^2 + 11x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{3x + 4} * {2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)} * {(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 4)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 8x + 3)/(6x^2 + 23x + 20)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 3)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}*{2x + 3}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{3x + 5}*{3x + 2}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 5x + 1)/(6x^2 + 19x + 10)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{3x + 5} * {3x + 5}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{2x + 1}*{2x + 3}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5}*{3x + 4}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{3x + 2} * {3x + 2}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{3x + 2} * {3x + 2}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{2x + 3}*{3x + 5}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{2x + 3} * {2x + 3}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 1)} * {(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{3x + 4}*{3x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{3x + 4} * {3x + 4}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(6x^2 + 13x + 6)/(9x^2 + 18x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{3x + 1} * {3x + 2}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{2x + 3} * {2x + 3}/{2x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 3)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{3x + 1} * {3x + 1}/{3x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 1)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 20x + 25)/(9x^2 + 18x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 5}/{3x + 1} * {2x + 5}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)} * {(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(4x^2 + 4x + 1)/(6x^2 + 19x + 15)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5} * {2x + 5}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{2x + 1}*{3x + 2}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{2x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 5)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{3x + 2} * {3x + 2}/{2x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 1}/{2x + 1} * {2x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{2x + 3}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{3x + 2}*{2x + 1}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 15x + 4)/(4x^2 + 16x + 15)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)(2x + 3)}\\)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{(2x + 1)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{3x + 2}*{2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(9x^2 + 30x + 25)/(6x^2 + 11x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{3x + 1} * {3x + 5}/{2x + 3}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}*{2x + 5}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 5}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)} * {(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}*{3x + 4}/{3x + 4}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 4}/{3x + 1}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}}/{{1}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 1}/{3x + 5} * {3x + 5}/{3x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({3x + 5}/{2x + 5} * {2x + 5}/{3x + 2}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 5)}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 5}/{3x + 2}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)} * {(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 1}/{3x + 4}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{2x + 5}*{3x + 2}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({3x + 2}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(2x + 1)}/{(2x + 3)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 1}/{2x + 5}*{2x + 3}/{2x + 1}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 1)(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}\\)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{(2x + 3)}/{(3x + 2)}}/{{(2x + 5)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n\\({2x + 3}/{3x + 2} * {3x + 2}/{2x + 5}\\)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}\\)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get \\({2x + 3}/{2x + 5}\\) as the answer.", "alternatives": ["\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 5)}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}"]}
]}